<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
        <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
        <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR></MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
        <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
        <CERTIFIED>N</CERTIFIED>
    </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <ASP>
      <ASP_Member>N</ASP_Member>
    </ASP>
    <Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Eyeo GmbH</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>Lichtstraße 25</Address_1>
        <City_Town>Cologne</City_Town>
        <State_Province>NRW</State_Province>
        <Zip_Postal_Code>50825</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>Germany</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>https://eyeo.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
        <Contact_Info>
            <Author_First_Name>Wladimir</Author_First_Name>
            <Author_Last_Name>Palant</Author_Last_Name>
            <Author_Email>trev@adblockplus.org</Author_Email>
            <Contact_First_Name>Christian</Contact_First_Name>
            <Contact_Last_Name>Dommers</Contact_Last_Name>
            <Contact_Email>christian@adblockplus.org</Contact_Email>
        </Contact_Info>
        <Support_Info>
            <Sales_Email>christian@adblockplus.org</Sales_Email>
            <Support_Email>info@adblockplus.org</Support_Email>
            <General_Email>info@adblockplus.org</General_Email>
            <Sales_Phone>+4922165028598</Sales_Phone>
            <Support_Phone>+4922165028598</Support_Phone>
            <General_Phone>+4922165028598</General_Phone>
            <Fax_Phone>+4922165028599</Fax_Phone>
        </Support_Info>
    </Company_Info>
    <Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>Adblock Plus for Safari</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>1.8.3</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>06</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>03</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2014</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Mac OS X</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>Arabic,Bengali,Bulgarian,Catalan,ChineseSimplified,ChineseTraditional,Croatian,Czech,Danish,Dutch,English,Estonian,Finnish,French,German,Greek,Hebrew,Hindi,Hungarian,Indonesian,Italian,Japanese,Kannada,Korean,Latvian,Lithuanian,Malay,Persian,Polish,Portuguese,Romanian,Russian,Serbian,Slovak,Slovenian,Spanish,Swedish,Tamil,Telugu,Thai,Turkish,Ukrainian,Vietnamese,Other</Program_Language>
        <Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_System_Requirements>Safari 6 or higher</Program_System_Requirements>
        <File_Info>
            <File_Size_Bytes>505597</File_Size_Bytes>
            <File_Size_K>493.75</File_Size_K>
            <File_Size_MB>0.49</File_Size_MB>
        </File_Info>
        <Expire_Info>
            <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
        </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Category_Class>Network &amp; Internet::Ad Blockers</Program_Category_Class>
        <FacebookProductPage>https://www.facebook.com/adblockplus</FacebookProductPage>
        <GooglePlusProductPage>https://plus.google.com/+AdblockPlus</GooglePlusProductPage>
    </Program_Info>
    <Program_Descriptions>
        <English>
            <Keywords>adblock, adblocker, Adblock Plus, security, privacy, Safari, YouTube</Keywords>
            <Char_Desc_45>Blocks all annoying ads on the web.</Char_Desc_45>
            <Char_Desc_80>Blocks all annoying ads online: also YouTube ads, pop-ups, banners, Facebook ads</Char_Desc_80>
            <Char_Desc_250>Browse the Internet without annoying ads with the best adblocker for Safari! Adblock Plus for Safari blocks all YouTube ads, pop-ups, banners, Facebook and Twitter ads.</Char_Desc_250>
            <Char_Desc_450>Adblock Plus for Safari automatically removes: YouTube ads, including the 30-second preroll ads, Facebook ads, Banners, Pop-ups, All other annoying ads.The most popular adblocker is highly customizable and includes an option to block tracking and malware. Unlike other adblocking solutions for Mac OS X, Adblock Plus for Safari blocks all YouTube ads. It is also the only adblocker for Safari that shows how many ads you block in each site.</Char_Desc_450>
            <Char_Desc_2000>Browse the Internet without annoying ads with the best adblocker for Safari!

Our Safari adblocker blocks all YouTube ads, pop-ups, banners and even the ads in your Facebook and Twitter feeds. Adblock Plus is the world's most popular browser extension, used by tens of millions of users all around the world.

Adblock Plus blocks all intrusive ads. Under default settings it supports websites and encourages better advertising by allowing non-annoying ads (configurable).

Adblock Plus for Safari automatically removes:
* YouTube ads, including the 30-second preroll ads
* Facebook ads
* Banners
* Pop-ups
* All other annoying ads

The most popular adblocker is highly customizable and includes an option to block tracking and malware. Unlike other adblocking solutions for Mac OS X, Adblock Plus for Safari is the only tool that blocks all YouTube ads. It is also the only adblocker for Safari that shows how many ads you block in each site.

Adblock Plus is also available for Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Opera, Internet Explorer and Android.

By supporting our Acceptable Ads initiative, you allow ads through which meet our criteria. By doing so, you support websites that rely on advertising but choose to do it in a non-intrusive way. This feature can be disabled at any time. Go to http://adblockplus.org/en/acceptable-ads to find out more.

Download Adblock Plus for Safari for free and browse the Internet without annoying ads!</Char_Desc_2000>
        </English>
        <German>
            <Keywords>adblock, Werbeblocker, Adblock Plus, Sicherheit, Privatsphäre, Safari, YouTube</Keywords>
            <Char_Desc_45>Blockiert störende Werbung im Netz</Char_Desc_45>
            <Char_Desc_80>Blockt störende Online-Werbung: YouTube- und Facebook Werbung, Pop-Ups, Banner</Char_Desc_80>
            <Char_Desc_250>Erlebe das Internet ohne störende Werbung mit dem besten Adblocker für Safari! Adblock Plus für Safari blockiert jede YouTube-, Facebook- und Twitter Werbung sowie Pop-Ups und Banner.</Char_Desc_250>
            <Char_Desc_450>Adblock Plus für Safari entfernt automatisch Facebook Werbung, Banner, Pop-Ups, Alle andere nervige Werbeformate. Der weltweit bekannteste Werbeblocker ist sehr flexibel und beinhaltet eine Anti -Tracking und -Malware Option. Im Gegensatz zu anderen Adblocking-Lösungen für Mac OS X, ist die ABP Version für Safari die einzige, die jede Werbung auf YouTube ausschaltet und zudem anzeigt wie viele Anzeigen pro Seite blockiert werden.</Char_Desc_450>
            <Char_Desc_2000>Erlebe das Internet ohne störende Werbung mit dem besten Adblocker für Safari!

Unser Adblocker für Safari unterdrückt sämtliche YouTube Werbung, Pop-Ups, Banner und sogar die Anzeigen auf Facebook und Twitter. Adblock Plus ist die weltweit-bekannteste Browser-Erweiterung und wird von Zig-Millionen Nutzern auf der ganzen Welt genutzt.

Adblock Plus unterdrückt jede aufdringliche Werbung. Werbung, die nicht störend ist wird gemäß Standardeinstellungen nicht blockiert.

Adblock Plus für Safari entfernt automatisch:
* YouTube Werbung, einschließlich 30-Sekunden Pre-Roll Spots
* Facebook Werbung
* Banner
* Pop-Ups
* Alle andere nervige Werbeformate

Der weltweit bekannteste Werbeblocker ist sehr anpassbar und beinhaltet eine Option, die es schafft Tracking und Malware zu blockieren. Im Gegensatz zu anderen Adblocking-Lösungen für Mac OS X, ist die Adblock Plus Version für Safari die einzige Anwendung, die jede Werbung auf YouTube ausschaltet. Zudem zeigt die Erweiterung als einzige für Safari an, wie viele Anzeigen tatsächlich pro Seite blockiert werden.

Adblock Plus ist auch erhältlich für Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Internet Explorer, Opera und Android.

Durch die Teilnahme an unserer Initiative für akzeptable Werbung ermöglichst du es der Werbung, die unseren Kriterien entspricht, durchgelassen zu werden. Auf diese Weise unterstützt du Webseiten, die auf ihre Werbung angewiesen sind, sich aber dazu entschieden haben, diese Werbung unaufdringlich und gewissenhaft zu gestalten. Diese Funktion kann jedoch jederzeit deaktiviert werden. Besuch unsere Webseite und erfahre mehr über unsere Initiative auf http://adblockplus.org/en/acceptable-ads

Lade dir Adblock Plus für Safari kostenfrei herunter und erlebe das Internet ohne störende Werbung!</Char_Desc_2000>
        </German>
        <Russian>
            <Keywords>adblock, adblocker, Adblock Plus, защита, конфиденциальность, Safari, YouTube</Keywords>
            <Char_Desc_45>Блокирует всю навязчивую рекламу в сети</Char_Desc_45>
            <Char_Desc_80>Блокирует навязчивую рекламу: на YouTube, в Facebook, всплывающие окна, баннеры</Char_Desc_80>
            <Char_Desc_250>Работайте в Интернет без навязчивой рекламы с лучшим блокировщиком рекламы для Safari! Adblock Plus для Safari блокирует всю рекламу на YouTube, всплывающие окна, баннеры, рекламу в Facebook и Twitter.</Char_Desc_250>
            <Char_Desc_450>Adblock Plus для Safari автоматически убирает: Рекламу на YouTube, включая 30-секундные ролики перед видео, рекламу на Facebook, баннеры, всплывающие окна, всю другую навязчивую рекламу. Являясь самым популярным блокировщиком рекламы, Adblock Plus является легко настраиваемым и включает в себя возможность блокирования отслеживание пользователя и блокирование вредоносных программ.</Char_Desc_450>
            <Char_Desc_2000>Навигация в Интернет без навязчивой рекламы с лучшим блокировщиком рекламы для Safari!

Наш блокировщик рекламы для Safari блокирует всю рекламу в YouTube, всплывающие окна, баннеры и даже рекламу в ваших Facebook и Twitter-лентах. Adblock Plus является самым популярным расширением для браузера в мире, используется десятками миллионов пользователей по всему миру.

Adblock Plus блокирует всю навязчивую рекламу. С настройками по умолчанию Adblock Plus поддерживает веб-сайты и поощряет хорошую рекламу, пропуская только ненавязчивую (настраивается).

Adblock Plus для Safari автоматически убирает:
* Рекламу на YouTube, включая 30-секундные ролики перед видео
* Рекламу на Facebook
* Баннеры
* Всплывающие окна
* Всю другую навязчивую рекламу

Являясь самым популярным блокировщиком рекламы, Adblock Plus прост в настройке и включает в себя возможность блокирования отслеживания пользователя, а также блокирования вредоносных программ. В отличие от других решений для блокировки рекламы для Mac OS X, Adblock Plus для Safari является единственным инструментом, который блокирует все объявления в YouTube. Это также единственный AdBlocker для Safari, который показывает, сколько объявлений вы блокируете на каждом сайте.

Adblock Plus также доступен для Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Internet Explorer, Opera, а также для Android.

Поддерживая нашу инициативу Ненавязчивой Рекламы, вы пропускаете рекламу, которая удовлетворяют наши условия. Поступая таким образом, вы поддерживаете сайты, которые полагаются на рекламу, но делают это в ненавязчивый способ. Эта функция может быть отключена в любое время. Перейдите на http://adblockplus.org/en/acceptable-ads, чтобы узнать больше.

Скачайте Adblock Plus для Safari бесплатно и работайте в Интернете без навязчивой рекламы!</Char_Desc_2000>
        </Russian>
        <Spanish>
            <Keywords>adblock, adblocker, Adblock Plus, seguridad online, privacidad, Safari, Anuncios YouTube</Keywords>
            <Char_Desc_45>Bloquea toda la publicidad molesta en la web</Char_Desc_45>
            <Char_Desc_80>Bloquea toda la publicidad molesta en la web, incluyendo en YouTube y Facebook</Char_Desc_80>
            <Char_Desc_250>Navega por la web sin publicidad molesta con el mejor bloqueador de publicidad para Safari. Bloquea toda la publicidad molesta en la web, incluyendo anuncios de video en YouTube y toda la publicidad en Facebook y Twitter.</Char_Desc_250>
            <Char_Desc_450>Adblock Plus para Safari bloquea por defecto todos los anuncios en YouTube y Facebook, Banners, ventanas emergentes y resto de publicidad molesta. Adblock plus es totalmente configurable, incluyendo opción de bloqueo de tracking y malware. A diferencia de otros bloqueadores de publicidad para Safari, Adblock Plus bloquea todos los anuncios en YouTube y es el único bloqueador que muestra cuántos anuncios se bloquean en cada web.</Char_Desc_450>
            <Char_Desc_2000>Navega por la web sin anuncios molestos con el mejor bloqueador de publicidad para Safari.

Adblock Plus para Safari bloquea todos los anuncios en YouTube, ventanas emergentes, banners e incluso los anuncios en el feed de Facebook y Twitter. Adblock Plus es la extensión para navegadores más popular del mundo y cada día es usado por decenas de millones de personas en todo el mundo.

Adblock Plus bloquea toda la publicidad intrusiva. Con la configuración por defecto, Adblock Plus permite mostrar anuncios no intrusivos y anima así a las webs a usar un mejor modelo de publicidad. Esta opción es configurable.

Adblock Plus para Safari bloquea automáticamente:
* Anuncios en YouTube, incluyendo los que se muestran al principio de algunos videos
* Anuncios en Facebook
* Banners
* Ventanas emergentes
* Resto de publicidad intrusiva

El adblocker más popular es altamente customizable e incluye opciones como bloquear tracking y dominios malware. A diferencia de otros programas para Mac OS X, Adblock Plus para Safari es la única herramienta que bloquea todos los anuncios en YouTube. También es el único adblocker para Safari que muestra cuántos anuncios estás bloqueando en cada web.

Adblock Plus también está disponible para Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, Opera y también el sistema operativo Android.

Apoyando la iniciativa de Anuncios Aceptables, permites que se muestren anuncios que cumplen con nuestros criterios, ayudando así a las webs que dependen de la publicidad pero deciden hacerlo de una manera no intrusiva. Esta opción puede ser activada en cualquier momento. Visita http://adblockplus.org/es/acceptable-ads para más información.

Descarga Adblock Plus para Safari totalmente gratis y navega por la web sin anuncios molestos.</Char_Desc_2000>
        </Spanish>
    </Program_Descriptions>
    <Web_Info>
        <Application_URLs>
            <Application_Info_URL>https://adblockplus.org</Application_Info_URL>
            <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://eyeo.com/pad/abp_screenshot.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
            <Application_Icon_URL>https://eyeo.com/pad/abp_icon.png</Application_Icon_URL>
            <Video_Link_1_URL>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pVYtzF5SemU</Video_Link_1_URL>
            <Application_XML_File_URL>https://eyeo.com/pad/abp_safari_pad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
        </Application_URLs>
        <Download_URLs>
            <Primary_Download_URL>https://downloads.adblockplus.org/adblockplussafari-1.8.3.safariextz</Primary_Download_URL>
        </Download_URLs>
    </Web_Info>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
